americanlaser.com 2013-05-08

# Privacy Policy | American Laser Skincare

## Introduction/Commitment

As a premier laser care service provider, American Laser Skincare is committed to protecting the privacy of all visitors to its Web site. It is our goal to maintain compliance with the highest standards of Web site privacy so our visitors may comfortably and safely use the site for a range of information needs. As used here, "American Laser Skincare" means American Laser Centers, LLC, and where appropriate, its affiliated organizations.

## What Information We Collect

Our system routinely collects information about origin and site navigation of Web site visitors. This information is used only to help us continually modify the site based on use patterns and is not linked to any personal identifying information. We do not collect any identifying or personal data on site users unless that information is submitted as part of a request for service or information, such as requesting an appointment. We do not currently use "cookies." A "cookie" is a text file placed on the browser of Web site visitors to identify Web site use patterns.

## Who Is Collecting the Information

The only people using aggregate Web site access information are American Laser Skincare employees, in particular, our web team. If a visitor submits additional identifying information (as noted above), that information is available only to American Laser Skincare staff.

## How We Will Use the Information

Information about Web site use patterns will be utilized by the web team and other appropriate American Laser Skincare staff to modify and enhance the Web site. Identifying individual information (such as name, e-mail and address) will be used only as requested by the visitor.

## With Whom Will the Information Be Shared

We do not sell, share or release any information about Web site users to any third parties, unless requested to do so by that user. Personal information about individual Web site users, as submitted as part of a service or information request, will not be shared in any way without specific consent from the user. However, we may disclose information when legally compelled to do so.

## Consumer Choices

Personal information about Web site users is collected only as part of a request for service. If information is required in order to provide a service, the Web site user will be informed as to which information is optional and which is essential for receipt of the service. Users have the option of asking that personal information be removed from our site once the service has been completed. Users also have the choice of ending any subscription or request for information by submitting a cancellation request to [consumer@americanlaser.com](mailto:consumer@americanlaser.com)

If users do not wish to have any "cookies" attached to their browser, they may disable cookies through their browser or Internet service company.

## E-mail Security

Our Web site offers opportunities to communicate with American Laser Skincare by e-mail. Because normal e-mail is not encrypted, the possibility exists that unauthorized individuals may intercept e-mail messages with American Laser Skincare. We are not responsible for the privacy of e-mail messages, except those stored in our system.

## Security Procedures/Access

Information sent by e-mail to American Laser Skincare will be accessed only by our staff as necessary to complete the function requested by the Web site visitor. The servers on which we store information are kept in a secure environment, behind a locked door, and are protected electronically from access by unauthorized individuals.

## Updating your Information

All information submitted to the American Laser Skincare Web site may be reviewed and changed. In order to review or change your information, contact us at [consumer@americanlaser.com](mailto:consumer@americanlaser.com)

## Notification of Changes

If American Laser Skincare changes this privacy statement, we will post those changes on the Web site so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. Any such changes shall be effective as of the date they are posted on the Web site.

[ ](http://www.americanlaser.com~/media/Files/PDF/Notice of Privacy Practices 2012.ashx) Click Here to View Notice of Privacy Practices
